funvideo.ca 2016-09-06

# 

Privacy Policy

We only collect anonymous information.  
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number or email address.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

We do not store or share your precise location.  
  
We do not use or collect your precise geographic location.

You can request to see or delete your personal data.  
  
You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

We keep personal data for a limited period.  
  
Our systems are designed to retain log data for up to one month after it is collected. We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account.

We don't share your personal data with other companies.  
We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.

No ad companies collect data through our service.  
We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting.

You can ask privacy questions.  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
support at funvideo.ca

Analytics providers access data on our behalf.  
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

We take steps to protect personal information  
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

You can review more privacy-related information.  
This privacy policy was last updated on March 4 2013. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
